welikela.com 2019-07-09

# We Like L.A. Privacy Policy and Legal Terms of Service -

The privacy of all We Like L.A. readers is extremely important to us and we have prepared this Privacy Policy to explain to you how we collect, use, and share information we obtain through your use of the this site and the services provided.

This policy is effective: 2/10/2015.

To contact us regarding this policy, or make inquiries regarding any of the below points, please email at: contact@welikela.com

### 1\. Collection of Personal Data

We automatically collect certain information to help us understand how our users use the Services (which we will refer to in this Privacy Policy collectively as “Usage Data”). For example, each time you visit the Services we may automatically collect your IP address, browser and computer type, access time, the Web page you came from, the URL you go to next, and the Web page(s) that you access during your visit.

We will use such Usage Data to diagnose problems with our servers and software, to administer the Services, and to gather demographic information. Our third-party advertising networks and servers will also provide us reports that will tell us how many ads were presented and clicked on the Services in a manner that does not identify personally any individual.

We may set and access cookies on your computer. Upon your first visit to the Services, a cookie is sent to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. A “cookie” is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer and stored on your hard drive when you visit a website. Many major Web services use cookies to provide useful features for their users. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent; however if you reject cookies, you will not be able to sign in to the Services or take full advantage of our Services.

We also may allow certain analytic services and providers of applications used on the Services (e.g., sharing buttons) to collect Non-Personally Identifiable information by placing cookies on the Services that will track certain performance of our Services, such as, web traffic, click-throughs, etc., in order to assist us and our service providers in better understanding the interests of our users and to better serve those interests.

### 2\. Usage of User Information

_A) General Practices_

Except as otherwise described in this section of our Privacy Policy, we will never share your Usage Data, Personal Information, Non-Personal Information, or Shared Information (which we will refer to in this Privacy Policy collectively as “User Information”) with any third party without your permission.

_B) Advertising_

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website. Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on previous web behavior. Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting **[Google Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/)**. (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting **[aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/)**.) Furthermore, from time to time, we may share your Usage Data and Non-Personal Information to enable third parties who serve advertisements on the Services to deliver advertisements that will be relevant to you. We will not share any such information, however, in a manner that would enable the advertiser to personally identify you.

_C) Aggregated Data_

From time to time, we may share aggregated User Information with third parties. We will not share any aggregated data, however, in manner that would enable the recipient to personally identify you.

_D) Public Information_

If you identify any User Information as public, you are authorizing us to share such information publicly. For example, you may elect to make certain Shared Information (such as your alias, bio, email or photos) publicly available. Also, there may be areas of the Services (e.g., message boards, discussion rooms, and other online forums) in which you are able to post information that will be available to all other users of the Services. By choosing to use these areas, you understand and agree that anyone may access, use, and disclose any information that you post to those areas.

_E) Legal action & Other Disclosure Scenarios_

Notwithstanding anything in this Privacy Policy to the contrary, we reserve the right, and you hereby expressly authorize us, to share any User Information: (1) in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish, protect, or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; (2) if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, fraud, or situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person or property; (3) if we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding significant abuse of the Services’ infrastructure or the Internet in general (such as voluminous spamming, denial of service attacks, or attempts to compromise the security of information); and (4) if we are acquired by or merged with another entity.

Furthermore, the User declares to be aware that the Data Controller may be required to reveal personal data upon request of public authorities.

### The rights of Users

We use reserve the right to use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see:  **[http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)**

### Image Terms of Use

We Like L.A. typically display images as part of blog posts written by our editors. The types of images editors are authorized to use on We Like L.A. sites include:

  * Images licensed from photographic archive vendors
  * Images supplied to our editors or released into the public domain by public relations and marketing companies for press purposes
  * Reader-submitted images, with the implied representation that the person submitting the image owns the copyright in the image and the right to give it to us for use on our site(s)
  * Images published on Flickr or other public photo sites in instances where the photographer has chosen to license their work under the Creative Commons license
  * Images commissioned by We Like L.A.
  * Images used to illustrate a newsworthy story under the Fair Use doctrine
  * Images where the use is transformative, such as for satire
  * Images so widely distributed on the internet that they are deemed to have become part of the public domain

If you think we have published an image or text that infringes your copyright, we will address your concerns; however, if the image falls into one of the categories listed above, we believe that our use of the image is legitimate and we will not remove it from the site.

Please note that we will respond only to notices of alleged infringement that comply with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act. The text of the Act can be found at the U.S. Copyright Office Web Site, http://lcWeb.loc.gov/copyright/

To file a notice of infringement with us, you must provide a written communication by email with an attached and signed PDF, including the following details:

  1. For each allegedly infringing image or piece of text that you wish to have removed from one of our sites, provide the exact permanent URL for the page containing the material.
  2. Provide information reasonably sufficient to permit us to contact you: an email address is preferred, as well as a telephone contact number.
  3. Provide the following information detailing your claim to ownership of the copyright in the allegedly infringing material:  
• Proof of copyright in the image or text concerned, namely proof of registration of the Image under the DMCA,OR, absent such registration,•a detailed description of where the photograph was taken, by whom, who or what the subject of the image is, AND  
• Evidence to support your claim that you own the copyright in the imageWe will not comply with requests to remove an image where the complainant cannot prove that they own the copyright in the image in question.
  4. Include the following statement: “I swear, under penalty of perjury, that the information in the notification is accurate and that I am the copyright owner or am authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.”

### System Logs and Maintenance

For operation and maintenance purposes, this Application and any third party services may collect files that record interaction with this Application (System Logs) or use for this purpose other Personal Data (such as IP Address).

### Information not contained in this policy

More details concerning the collection or processing of Personal Data may be requested from We Like L.A. at any time. Please see the contact information at the beginning of this document.

### Questions and Changes to This Policy

We Like L.A. reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time by giving notice to its Users on this page. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the bottom. If a User objects to any of the changes to the Policy, the User must cease using this Application and can request that the Data Controller removes the Personal Data. Unless stated otherwise, the then-current privacy policy applies to all Personal Data the Data Controller has about Users.

For further inquires or questions, please write via email to: contact@welikela.com
